### Contact

bstefansen11@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/blakestefansen (LinkedIn) bstefansen.github.io/Portfolio/ (Portfolio) github.com/bstefansen (Other)

### Top Skills

**JavaScript** 

React.js

Node.js

### Certifications

Responsive Web Design
JavaScript Algorithms and Data
Structures

Information Security and Quality Assurance

**Data Visualization** 

Front End Libraries

#### Honors-Awards

Honors Graduate

Charles L. Blount Scholarship

Florida Bright Futures Scholarship

Florida Credit Union Scholarship

The Education Foundation Senior Scholarship

# Blake Stefansen

MERN // Full Stack Developer

Gainesville, Florida

### Summary

I'm a University of Florida graduate with a passion for user experience and front-end design using the MERN technology stack. I specialize in JavaScript and also have experience with GIS products and photoshop.

Take a look at my portfolio, and let's get in touch! ➡#https://bstefansen.github.io/Portfolio/

## Experience

TERRA-COM Environmental Consulting, Inc. Associate Field Geologist May 2019 - June 2019 (2 months)

Collaborated with geologists in preparation of site assessments, data evaluation, HASP's, and report writing. Executed groundwater sampling field services compliant with FDEP regulations.

Florida Credit Union Office Assistant January 2016 - April 2019 (3 years 4 months) Gainesville, Florida

Launched first annual cost analysis report of office supplies, informing senior management of decisions for optimizing annual savings. Developed and managed ordering systems for company supplies, streamlining ordering procedures for company branches and departments. Reduced vendor pricing of office supplies. Drafted and optimized procedures for diverse office tasks. Supervised inventory of corporate office to enhance workflow for office personnel.

Walgreens
Customer Service Representative
October 2015 - December 2015 (3 months)

Managed the front register and interacted with customers. Responsibilities included maintaining receipts, answering incoming phone requests, giving appropriate change, requesting price checks, and ringing up sales.

## Education

University of Florida

Certificate, Geospatial Information Analysis (GIS) · (2019 - 2020)

University of Florida

Bachelor's degree, Geology · (2018 - 2020)

Santa Fe College

Associate of Arts - AA, Geology · (2017 - 2018)